Inventory of the Dora and Cara Armistead Papers 1880-1950
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Mss. Acc. 2006.54, 1880-1950; id60351
  - Other Family Materials, id61617
    - Photographs. Note that, when possible, the photographs have been removed from the original folder, envelope or sleeve. When done, the original folder or sleeve has been filed with its accompanying photograph. These items are included in the item total for each folder (i.e., one photograph and 
      - Photos of Historic Items and One of the Pulaski Club (Note that some photos have duplicates, which are stored in the same sleeve). 13 items., id62106 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Scaling Photos of Plaster Architectural Fragments. 14 items., id62107 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Photo of Shirley Temple with Facsimile Autograph and a Photo of a Painting of Winston Churchill. 3 items., id62108 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Two Photos of the Jones House (Now Restored as the Surveyor’s Office) and an Unidentified House. 5 items., id62109 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Photos of Cara and One Possibly of Meriwether Armistead. 7 items., id62110 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified Portraits. 31 items., id62111 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Photos of Classes and Groups (Unidentified). 5 items., id62112 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Photos from an Outdoor Fair. 4 items., id62113 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Photos of Colonial Williamsburg Sites (Including the Cary Armistead House), and an Unidentified Factory. 7 items., id62114 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - A Box of Virginia Law Firm Cards and an Unidentified, Extremely Fragile Rolled Photograph., id62077 (Box 15)
    - Armistead Family Education and Teaching Materials, id61618 (Sub-series 1)
    - Armistead Family Social, Cultural,and Property Materials., id61620 (Sub-series 2)
    - Eastern Lunatic Asylum (now Eastern State Hospital) Materials., id61621 (Sub-series 3)
      - Cary Armistead – Eastern Lunatic Asylum (now Eastern State Hospital) Materials. See Box I for financial materials., id62074 (Sub-series 3, Box 12)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Contract Bidding Materials. 13 items., id62185 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 1)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Menus. 3 items., id62186 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 2)
        - Letters of Recommendation of Cary Armistead to Eastern Lunatic Asylum Steward’s Position. 7 items., id62187 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Annual Report, 1886. 1 item., id62188 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Carpentry Correspondence and Lists. 4 items., id62189 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 5)
        - Letters and Lists From and Concerning Patients at Eastern Lunatic Asylum. 23 items., id62190 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 6)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Bills, Payroll and Financial Materials. 25 items., id62191 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 7)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Bills, Payroll and Financial Materials. 26 items., id62192 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 8)
        - Eastern Lunatic Asylum Correspondence. 21 items., id62193 (Sub-series 3, Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Armistead Family Issues and Interests, id61623 (Sub-series 4)
    - Photographs, id61624 (Sub-series 5)
    - Armistead Family Interest Materials., id61626 (Sub-series 6)
      - Armistead Family Interest Materials, id62078 (Sub-series 6, Box 16)
        - Food Competition Award Ribbons – 1938 Virginia State Fair. 6 items, id62079 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 1)
        - 1896 Book: The Battle of Chancellorsville: Jackson’s Attack – Includes Iinscription, “Compliments of the Author, and Genl. James H. Lane.” 1 item., id62080 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 2)
        - Sons of the American Revolution Magazine, January, 1931, Volume XXV, Number 3. 1 item., id62081 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Psalm Book: Daily Food. 1 item., id62082 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Various Calling Cards. 3 items., id62083 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 5)
        - Book: Fancy Work and Art Decorations with Diamond Dyes by Nella Daggett. 1 item., id62084 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 6)
        - Music Recital Flyers. 2 items., id62085 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 7)
        - Lists of Indeterminate Origin and Purpose. 14 items., id62086 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 8)
        - James City County Levy Information, 1895-6. 2 items., id62087 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 9)
        - Williamsburg Lodge Postcard and Menu. 2 items., id62088 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 10)
        - Notary Public Commission for Mary Taliaferro. 2 items., id62090 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 11)
        - Four Poems – One by Col. R.H. Armistead, One by “M.L.P.,” Two Clipped from Newspapers. 4 items., id62091 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 12)
        - Bylaws of the Williamsburg Yacht Club. 1 item., id62092 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 13)
        - Virginia Bar Weekly, January 5, 1943. 1 item., id62093 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 14)
        - Newspaper Scraps and Clippings. 5 items., id62094 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 15)
        - Valentine’s Day Cards. 5 items., id62095 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 16)
        - Advertisements and Handbills. 8 items., id62096 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 17)
        - Unused Postcards. 6 items., id62097 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 18)
        - Envelope of Hair Labeled “Meriwether’s Hair.” 1 item., id62098 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 19)
        - 1959 VA State Fair Guide/Premium List. 2 items., id62099 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 20)
        - John Charles and the "Model School", 1894, 1995 and 1914; id70925 (Sub-series 6, Box 16, Folder 21)
- Mss. Acc. 2004.24, 1905, 1906, 1907; id60352